---

---

Privacy Policy
--------------

This Privacy Policy describes how Tron-Free.com store and deal with your user information. You can only use the service of tron-free.com if you agree to this Privacy Policy.  

To create an account, we will collect your username, email, password.

We use this information to allow you to login and operate your account securely.

Wallet address is collected to send you payment when you make a withdrawal.

We may log usage data about your use of our website. The usage data include:

IP address, country location, internet service provider, browser, and device Information, date and time of Log In.

We use this information to operate, maintain our website and service. Prevent your account from unauthorized access or operation by others.

We use third party offerwalls and survey partners to provide offers and surveys, you will need to review the privacy policy of every service you visit and use. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for that.

It is optional to provide your full name, country, address and personal photo to complete the offer system verification. We use this to prevent offer abuse, you may request to delete this at any time.

We store your personal data as securely as we can on secure servers. Reasonable steps necessary to ensure your data is adequately protected, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

You have the right to access any personal information that Tron-Free processes about you.

You have the right to request to delete your personal information.

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data. This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it.

###### We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 16 or knowingly allow such persons to provide us with their personal information without parent or guardian consent. If you are under the age of 16, do not send any information about yourself to us or signup for an account.

###### If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child under the age of 16 years old has provided us with information without your consent, please contact us and we will take steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our systems.

We do not share or disclose any of your personal information without your consent, other than for the purposes specified in this notice or where there is a legal requirement.

Retention of data

We will also retain usage data for internal analysis purposes. Usage data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our service.

We maintain your personal data until and unless you request account deletion, at which time we will delete all personal information without undue delay.

We use host in Germany. We may also use some products or services like email hosting that may be hosted in non-EU countries. Your consent to this privacy policy represents your agreement to that transfer.

We will take steps to ensure that those providers use the necessary level of protection for your information and abide by strict agreements and measures set out by the globally required standard.

We use Google Analytics to monitor and analyze how our Service is used.

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the [Google Privacy Terms](https://policies.google.com/privacy) web page.

Our service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. We use this information to identify a user, to save certain settings that are important to the account usage.

We welcome your comments or questions about this privacy policy. You may also contact us at: Mail: [\[email protected\]](https://tron-free.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) | Telegram: [https://t.me/tronfreechat](https://t.me/tronfreechat)

English is the main language of this website. Any other language is translated from that main language and should any doubts arise when using any those languages, then the English version shall prevail. We decline any responsibility in the case of an incorrect translation.

We may update and change this privacy policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website. If we make any changes, we will change the last updated date below. This Privacy Policy was last Updated on 03/06/2021.

Social Network:    [](https://www.facebook.com/tronfree/ "Facebook")    [](https://twitter.com/TronFree1 "Twitter")   [](https://t.me/tronfreechat "Telegram")
